Can't we just go home in that?
- Can we?
- Should we ask?
- This is Opera. Fish, do you copy?
- Yes, let's ask.
- Do choppers usually wobble like that?
- This is Opera. Fish, do you copy?
I've never seen one before,
so I'm not sure.
But it is swaying quite a bit, sir.
Maybe it's because the wind
is blowing too strongly.
This is Opera. Fish, do you copy?
This is Opera. Respond, over.
- Kyung-sik!
- Private Hwang Kyung-sik, sir!
- Are they responding?
- Negative, sir.
The pilot seems inexperienced,
so stay alert.
- Yes, sir.
- Sir!
- Don't do it.
- What is it now?
Will you be quiet?
You idiot!
Hey, you punk!
What's he doing?
Don't cross the helipad! Focus, damn it!
You piece of shit!
You cannot let them land, sir!
Look at this!
Shit.
What?
This is Opera. Fish, do you copy?
Can you please just walk straight?
Hold on. Are there any zombies here?
Let's go in here.
Get in there.
- Damn it, go your own way.
- Let me in!
Stop following us.
Shit.
No zombies?
My head is killing me.
Look at that.
They have oriental raisin tea.
Let's drink some more.
- Drink up, Tripeater.
- Okay.
Cheers, Boozer.
- Seriously, they're both crazy.
- Drink up.
- What's going on?
- Fire in the hole!
- Zombies.
- It's zombies!
- Fire in the hole!
- That's freaking sick.
- Hey, that's Alex.
- Where?
- Hi, Alex.
- Alex, over here!
Oh no.
- You killed it!
- That was so dope.
- Let's cheers to that.
- Can we replay that?
This is ridiculous.
- Cheers!
Lay off the booze, damn it!
You drink this.
Gross.
Damn it.
- Jin-wook!
- Huh?
- Hey, open the door!
- Where's my beer?
- It's Alex.
- What am I? A fucking doormat?
- Fuck.
- I'm coming. Hold on.
Hurry up!
- Quick!
- Alex, come on!
Alex!
I think I drank too much.
- That was awesome.
- Are you guys okay?
Can you do that again?
Look, it's zombies.
- They're baseball players.
- That's it.
They're fighting again.
Go, Twins!
No, the Giants are the best.
You're wrong.
- Get them, Giants!
- Kiwoom Heroes all the way.
- Go, Twins! You can do it!
- Go, Giants!
Let's go!
Raise your rifles!
Lock and load on the chopper!
Air defense squad, to your positions!
- What?
To your positions!
Target approaching at four o'clock!
This is as far as it will go, sir.
Prepare to fire!
Engage the chopper's tail!
- Damn it.
- Get it together!
Do you want to go home in a box?
Shit.
Aim and fire!
- Aim and fire!
Get the tail!
- Yes, sir!
Private Ra In-ho, aiming at the tail!
- Is it within range?
- Closing in, sir!
Shoot it down!
Target locked! One, two!
Commencing fire!
I feel like shit.
Hey, what's that?
There's no time for this. Lead the way.
They're gone.
- Get Young-joo.
- Come here.
- I feel horrible.
- Watch your step.
- Look at that.
- Hang in there, okay?
Damn, I feel like throwing up.
Let's hurry.
Who cares how much a chopper costs
in this situation?
Did you just yell at me?
Are you fucking crazy?
Get your head straight!
I'm sorry, sir.
Battalion Commander,
if you can't send us supplies,
please allow us to relocate
to the base camp at Suseo Station.
If we stay here,
we'll run out of food and water.
We won't last more than a few days.
We'll figure out a way to join the ranks
at Suseo Station's base camp--
Negative. Cut the nonsense
and stand by at your current location.
Yes, sir.
I'll monitor the situation
and get back to you.
Until then, stand by.
Yes, sir. Understood.
Salute.
That fucking bastard.
Is he telling us to stay holed up
in this fucking place and die?
All right, listen up.
Here's the bottom line.
We're leaving this building today.
- What?
- Sir?
Is it to get supplies from the brigade?
Unfortunately,
there won't be any resupply.
We can go a few weeks without food, sir.
That's right, sir.
We still have running water.
I know there's enough water
in the hotel water tank.
But we'll lose power in a few days.
When that happens,
it'll cut off our water supply.
If that's the case,
can't we leave when the water is cut off?
Sir?
Do you think we can put up a fight
on just water alone?
Dang it.
It's better to make a move
while we still have the energy left.
Since it's come down to this,
our only option is to fight like hell
to make it out of here alive.
What is it?
May I...
have a gun?
Given the situation we're in,
I'm really trying to go easy on you
about what happened last night.
So please don't cross the line.
Didn't you see me shoot yesterday?
I competed as a shooter in high school
and made it to the national reserve team.
I'm pretty sure I'm a better shooter
than most of the men here.
You can test me if you want.
Please let me...
fight for my own life.
- Damn.
- Holy shit.
- Shit.
- Unbelievable.
What the hell?
I can't believe this is Gangnam.
This isn't what I expected to see.
This place has been wiped out, too.
Damn it, what a fucking grand reception.
911 EMERGENCY
It seems they called an ambulance.
Are you sure there are soldiers here?
Jae-yoon.
Hey, where are you going?
You're not going in there, are you?
Are you out of your mind?
Don't you see that?
- Are you trying to get killed?
- Hey.
He's right, though.
We'll die if we go in now.
Let's go somewhere safe
and wait to hear from your boyfriend.
Okay? I'm sure he'll call you.
Let's go down to the parking lot for now.
Yeah, don't worry too much.
Let's just go for now.
Come on, let's go.
You can't get through that.
He's right. Come on, Boozer. Let's go.
Come on.
They drove right into the middle.
- Jae-yoon.
- It's like a zombie convention, right?
Shit, what a mess.
- Is this the only way in?
- It's a fucking mess.
It looks like a hiding spot for zombies.
- Is there anything in the car?
- Look at all this blood.
It's empty.
- Are you sure about this?
- Hey, slow down.
Hold on.
Let's split up and look for my car.
It's a navy Hummer. Plate number 4574.
- Are you sure it's in this zone?
- I don't know.
A navy Hummer. Plate number 4574.
How can you not remember
where you parked your own car?
I used the valet service
because I'm a VVIP.
- About earlier...
- What's a "VVIP"?
- "Very, Very Important Person."
- Sorry I lost my temper.
But you know...
You were in the wrong.
You'd be dead if you went inside.
- Hey, what's that?
- You know that, right?
- Young-joo!
- Run!
- Move! Hurry!
- Get out of there!
- The zombies are coming!
- Fuck!
Run!
No.
What the fuck?
Get away from me, you piece of shit!
Go away!
Young-joo!
- Alex!
- Hey, stop! That's suicide!
Let go, Jin-wook!
Just fucking listen to me, damn it!
No, Alex!
- No.
- Die!
No! Alex!
Alex!
No! Please!
No!
I know you're all scared.
But we have to overcome this.
Why is that, Hwang Kyung-sik?
Private Hwang Kyung-sik.
It's because we serve
the Republic of Korea, sir.
Save that for the president.
Yes, sir!
Do you know what true victory is?
It's to survive.
Survival is the ultimate victory.
"To live, you must be willing to die.
To fear death is to ensure it."
What does that mean?
It means we need to fight to survive.
If we hold back in fear, we'll die.
Correct.
We fight to the death
so we can make it back home.
- Yes, sir!
That's the spirit.
We'll take the stairs to the VIP lounge.
From there, we'll take the elevator.
Okay, let's head out.
Kim Young-man, Kwak Gye-young.
Get the door.
- Yes, sir.
Hold fire until I give the order.
Understood?
- Yes, sir.
- Selector switch to semi.
- Switching to semi.
On the count of three.
One.
Two.
Three.
Shit, what's this smell?
What is all this?
Hey!
I don't think the car's over here!
Go check if it's in another zone!
What's he doing?
Loser.
What the fuck is wrong with you,
you fucking bastard?
I'm going to kill you
when I get my hands on you!
You fucking piece of shit!
So, what do you want me to do?
Why you little...
Just go look for the car.
When you find it, bring it over here.
I don't know how to drive.
Why the hell didn't you get your license?
I was trying to get into college!
Keep this up, and I'm out of here.
Okay, I'm sorry. Just hold on.
Hold on, damn it!
Your phone's not dead, right?
- Give me your number.
- What?
Your phone number.
- Keep your guard up.
- Be careful, sir.
Are they dead now?
Pick up the pace.
This is fucked up.
We're in the thick of it,
and he's hung up over the chopper's cost?
What about the cost of the chopper, sir?
He wants us to pay
for the chopper you shot down.
Oh, that supply chopper?
You're all accomplices,
so we're splitting the cost.
- But...
- Do I have to pay?
How much is a chopper?
- I don't know, sir.
- We're screwed.
- Shit.
- Do I really have to pay?
It was a joke.
Before we head down to the lobby,
we'll sweep the lounge in pairs.
If the coast is clear,
proceed with weapons maintenance.
The condition of your firearms
will dictate how the next fight goes.
Once that's done, we'll head to the lobby.
- Do you understand?
- Yes, sir.
Then start the sweep. Go.
You're with me.
How am I supposed to find it?
This is just...
What the hell?
304NO 4574
Oh, that's it. That's the car.
Plate number 4574. Yes!
Oh, god.
Sorry, zombies.
Can you get out of the way?
Excuse me.
Go away. There's nothing here.
BOOZER
I have no idea how this works.
VIDEO CALL
BOOZER
- Hello?
- Are you in the car?
- Yes.
- Can you start the engine?
No, I told you.
I did nothing but work and study.
Seriously?
Press the "engine start" button.
The "engine start" button?
I don't see it.
If it's a Hummer, you need the key.
Insert it and give it a turn.
Okay.
Is the engine running?
No, not yet. It's not working.
- Why isn't it working?
- Why won't it work?
- Step on the brake.
- You didn't step on the brake?
You didn't tell me to do that.
So, which one is the brake?
There are two pedals.
The left one, damn it!
I swear I'm going to get my license
as soon as this is over.
Okay, what's next?
Put the gear in drive
and step on the right pedal.
Hang on. I can't hold the phone
and grab the wheel at the same time.
There we go.
- Do I put on the seat belt?
- Do whatever you want.
- Just put it on.
- Okay.
He's acting so cocky
just because he knows how to drive.
What an asshole.
I'll be there soon.
Oh, fuck! Is this going to blow up?
What happened?
Take your foot off the brake, dumbass!
And lightly step on the gas.
Fuck.
Holy shit! I'm fucking driving.
Sorry, guys! I'm sorry!
Oh, shit.
This is going too fucking fast!
Help!
Do something!
- Don't jerk the wheel like that!
- I think I'm going to crash!
- Be quiet.
- This is going too fast!
- Don't jerk the wheel so much.
- No, wait!
Hey, are you listening to me?
- Hey!
- Keep your voice down.
Go slow and use the brake.
Private Lee, if we find a zombie here--
Keep your mouth shut.
Yes, sir.
In-ho.
Tell the admin supply officer
that the restrooms are clear.
I have a more pressing matter, sir.
- Sir.
- What?
There are food supplies here
and on the other end.
Okay.
We don't know how long
we'll be in isolation.
Grab food that is light and calorie-dense.
Have everyone put some in their gear
before we head down.
- Yes, sir.
- Oh, nice. I'm taking the nuts.
- Bananas...
- Private Lee.
- What?
Sir.
This is for you.
It was smart of you to
pack these red ginseng extracts.
You've got it covered
when it comes to things like this.
MY WIFE
- Private Lee.
- What?
We have Wi-Fi.
- We have Wi-Fi.
We have Wi-Fi?
The Wi-Fi is working. Hold on.
MY DARLING YOUNG-JOO
- That's it. Take it slow.
- Take your time.
SWEET JAE-YOON
What the...
Young-joo!
Jae-yoon!
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
No, I'm okay.
- Oh, thank god!
- Are you okay?
- Are you hurt?
- No, I'm fine.
I'm not hurt at all. Look.
- I'm so relieved.
- Where are you?
I'm in the basement of A Tower.
Are you still up there?
What?
What floor are you on? I'll come up.
- Wait--
- Just tell me, and I'll come to you.
Why on earth would you come here?
I was worried about you.
You shouldn't have come here, Young-joo.
Just tell me what floor you're on.
It's really dangerous here,
so you need to go somewhere safe.
Hey, I can't just leave you here.
- Just wait. I'm coming up.
- No, please don't.
You can't do that.
It's really dangerous here!
You have no idea
what I've been through.
I'm super strong. I'm stronger than you.
I'll protect you.
- Oh, come on.
- I'll come to you.
So just tell me where you are.
- Hold on. Hey, Young-joo.
- Yes?
I'm really sorry,
but I forgot to tell you
that I'm not at A Tower right now.
- What?
- So don't stay here...
- I mean, don't stay there--
- Suseo Station.
The Capital Defense Command
is setting up a base camp there.
That's what the first sergeant said
when he was talking to HQ.
- Jae-yoon?
- Go to Suseo Station.
Suseo Station?
That area is full of soldiers,
so it's the safest place.
Head over there,
and I'll be right behind you.
- Okay? I'll see you there.
- Jae-yoon.
-Young-joo, Suseo--
- Suseo...
Fuck!
Jae-yoon.
What the fuck?
- Private Lee--
- Hold on.
YOUNG-JOO, THE CALL GOT CUT...
It's a relief nothing bad happened to her.
If she's made it this far,
doesn't that mean
her chances of survival are good?
You're right, In-ho.
That gives me something to hold on to.
I just need to get out of here
and find Young-joo.
- What was that?
- Private Lee.
What happened?
What the heck? Why is it not connecting?
Was the call disconnected?
Hello? Hey!
Damn it.
I'm going way too fast.
I need to slow down,
or I'm going to crash.
I want to get off.
I can't do this anymore.
What was that noise?
- Get up, sir!
- What was that, Sergeant Kim?
- What happened?
- Oh, hey.
Kyung-sik and I took out four zombies.
You're the best, Sergeant Kim.
Don't let your guard down.
They jump out of nowhere.
- Yes, sir.
- They just appeared suddenly.
- Remember, aim for the head.
- Yes, sir.
The zombies came from up there,
but Kyung-sik and I got them all.
- How many did you get?
- That's not important!
- What the fuck?
- We need to move out.
Damn, I must've slipped.
- We should go, sir.
- Okay.
- I should take this, too.
- Something light...
- Papayas.
- This looks tasty.
- Oh, there's bread.
- Stop.
- Stop!
- What?
Hey, wait. Soo-jeong!
- Wait.
- Stop, Paolo!
What are you doing?
Don't you know soldiers can't be in here?
- Paolo.
- What?
- Paolo?
- Gye-young.
- Do not move!
- Sir.
Please don't shoot me.
Paolo.
Are you okay? Were you bitten?
Bitten?
- Tell him I need to check for bite marks.
- Okay.
- Gye-young.
- Yes, sir. Paolo.
He looks fine.
Are you here alone?
Yes, I'm alone.
People were fighting like crazy.
How were you asleep
with all that noise out there?
Are you on drugs?
How can a chef
be doing this sort of thing?
These aren't drugs.
They're sleeping pills.
Sleeping pills?
Hey, First Sergeant, I'm scared.
I want to go to the embassy.
Will you take me there?
We're not going there.
If you rescue a US citizen,
you have to take them to the US embassy.
We're not here to rescue you, Paolo.
Is this how you treat a US citizen?
Jeokbanhajang!
JEOKBANHAJANG:
BLAMING THE VICTIM
It's not a rescue mission. The embassy?
Don't you know what's going on out there?
- No, it's fine.
- Stop!
Sir, I think he slept through it all.
He doesn't seem to know
what's going on, sir.
Paolo, what's going on?
I want to get off. Get me out of here.
Hey, get out of the way! It's dangerous!
Get out of the way.
You guys should be more careful!
Get off me.
I feel like puking.
Get in the back seat.
I'll take it from here.
Get out of the way, you bastards!
Die!
Die, you fucking bastards!
- Stop it!
- You fucking zombies!
I'm going to puke.
- Die!
- I'm dizzy!
She says she's dizzy!
I'm begging you. Stop the car!
- Damn you all.
- Stop it!
Will you stop?
You're acting like a psycho!
Wouldn't it be better
to live like a psycho?
Well, I want to stay alive
one way or another.
But you need to stop.
It's making her dizzy.
Do you want to be acknowledged
for finding this damn car?
Did you fucking forget
we saved your sorry ass from the streets?
Know your place, Tripeater.
Do your parents know
you're out there getting wasted?
That's why you're not in college yet.
I feel sorry for your parents.
To think they raised you.
What the fuck, man?
I'm going to kill you if you don't let go.
You're the one who's got a death wish.
Should I leave you some teeth marks?
- Go ahead. Just bite him.
- Why you...
You'd better think twice
about the state I'm in.
Okay, point taken. Let go, please.
I got it.
I should just bite you.
I am grateful you kept me around
so I didn't feel lonely.
- But watch your language, okay?
- Okay.
Being rich doesn't make up
for being a jerk.
Right, Boozer?
- Fuck.
- Come on, let's go.
Sure.
Eat up. It might be a long stretch
before we eat again.
- Yes, sir!
- Yes, sir.
JUNG TAE-HWA
MAY 4, 2025
I'll charge you for this later.
Nothing's free in here.
I really hope I get to pay you later.
Sir.
This is a non-smoking hotel, sir.
He can fine me.
Have a smoke, all of you.
- Pass me one, Jae-yoon.
- Hey.
You can't smoke
in a Michelin-starred restaurant.
Damn it!
You're smoking, too?
Aren't you a staff member?
And you're vaping?
- Shit!
- Are you going somewhere, sir?
I'm getting a drink.
- I'll get it for you, sir.
- No, I can get it myself.
It's getting worse and worse! Fuck!
Paolo.
I'm fucking worried about Korea's future.
- What was that?
- What was that noise?
Sergeant Kim.
Wait, sir.
Sir?
Are you all right?
Sir, we're going to move in.
His legs...
Fuck.
- Sir.
- What?
Shit.
His nose.
The closer the bite is to the head,
the quicker the infection.
We'll head to Seoul Hospital first
then Suseo Station after that.
Seoul Hospital?
My mom's there.
I see. Is she unwell?
Oh, you didn't know?
She owns that hospital.
I have to go to Suseo Station.
Jae-yoon told me to come--
Don't you think he needs to get checked?
What?
We'll get you some help at the hospital,
so don't worry.
You're pretty banged up, too.
It's close to Suseo Station.
I'll drop you off at Suseo Station
after you get treated, okay?
Okay.
Hey, do it out the window.
I need to use the restroom. Pull over.
Where am I supposed to pull over, dumbass?
- Stop the car before I bite you!
- Okay, fine!
I'm pulling over. Shit.
- Damn it, he's fucking crazy.
- Hey.
Is there a restroom nearby?
Does it matter? I can puke anywhere.
That's gross. We're not friends anymore.
I want to go home and eat ramyeon
loaded with black pepper.
You eat it like that, too?
It's the best hangover cure.
You bet I do.
You know what's good, Boozer.
Don't call me Boozer.
I'm totally sober now.
I'm starting to sober up, too.
- I'm going to go home.
- What?
You should come with us
and get your leg checked.
- And Suseo Station--
- No, I'm scared of hospitals.
I hate them.
I'd rather go home and study.
You're going to study?
You're fucking crazy.
The world might recover from this
surprisingly quickly.
If I study while they're distracted,
I'll get ahead of them.
Go before it gets too dangerous.
I'll find my way home.
Okay, take care.
Let's head to the hospital.
Are you sure you'll be okay on your own?
Come on, Boozer.
It's "don't worry," you idiot.
You'd better go home and study hard.
Seems like you need it.
I will, so just get out of here, punk!
What, punk?
Step on the gas, you moron.
Wait.
- Hey, be careful.
- I will.
Be careful out there.
No! Leave them alone!
Will he be okay?
By the way, what was his name?
I should've gotten his name.
He was turning into a zombie.
He couldn't have stayed
with us much longer.
It's time we went our separate ways.
What an idiot.
Hey, stop it. Stay back, damn it!
You fuckers!
Damn, this is way easier than studying.